[{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664432784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":242089,"timeElapsed":593990},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8036,"timeElapsed":602027},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664457016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":16194,"timeElapsed":618222},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5688,"timeElapsed":623911},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664464886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":626092},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3948,"timeElapsed":630041},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":634008},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664479230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6428,"timeElapsed":640436},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664493589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":14358,"timeElapsed":654795},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664500468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5797,"timeElapsed":661674},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":38092,"timeElapsed":699767},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664556021,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17460,"timeElapsed":717227},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4929,"timeElapsed":722157},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664564813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3861,"timeElapsed":726019},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664569320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4507,"timeElapsed":730526},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664571982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":733188},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664575179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3196,"timeElapsed":736385},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7932,"timeElapsed":744317},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664603396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20284,"timeElapsed":764602},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664636409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":29400,"timeElapsed":797615},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664638723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2313,"timeElapsed":799929},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641405,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2682,"timeElapsed":802611},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664645443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4037,"timeElapsed":806649},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664674807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":29364,"timeElapsed":836013},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664677632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":838838},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664679506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1873,"timeElapsed":840712},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664687955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8449,"timeElapsed":849161},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664724399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":36443,"timeElapsed":885605},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664745092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":20693,"timeElapsed":906298},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":6720,"timeElapsed":913959},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2307,"timeElapsed":916266},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664757604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2544,"timeElapsed":918810},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664759501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1896,"timeElapsed":920707},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664761969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2467,"timeElapsed":923175},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664763864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1894,"timeElapsed":925070},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664765707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1843,"timeElapsed":926913},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664788765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":23057,"timeElapsed":949971},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664796046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7281,"timeElapsed":957252},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664801865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4998,"timeElapsed":963071},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664802983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1118,"timeElapsed":964189},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664804290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1306,"timeElapsed":965496},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664806584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":967790},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664807991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1407,"timeElapsed":969197},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664809045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1053,"timeElapsed":970251},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664810611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1566,"timeElapsed":971817},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664812401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":973607},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664814183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":975389},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664825804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10776,"timeElapsed":987010},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664828944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3140,"timeElapsed":990150},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664831274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":992480},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664833124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1849,"timeElapsed":994330},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664834782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1658,"timeElapsed":995988},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664836007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1224,"timeElapsed":997213},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664848810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12803,"timeElapsed":1010016},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664860368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11557,"timeElapsed":1021574},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664862287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1919,"timeElapsed":1023493},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664866842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3786,"timeElapsed":1028048},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664868510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1667,"timeElapsed":1029716},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664870115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1604,"timeElapsed":1031321},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664871599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1484,"timeElapsed":1032805},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664873127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1527,"timeElapsed":1034333},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664874954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1826,"timeElapsed":1036160},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664876352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1398,"timeElapsed":1037558},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664877925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1572,"timeElapsed":1039131},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664879451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1525,"timeElapsed":1040657},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664893370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4545,"timeElapsed":1054576},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664894800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1429,"timeElapsed":1056006},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664896382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1581,"timeElapsed":1057588},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664897918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1536,"timeElapsed":1059124},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664901163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":1062369},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664902164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1000,"timeElapsed":1063370},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664911161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8997,"timeElapsed":1072367},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664912664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1502,"timeElapsed":1073870},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664914189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1524,"timeElapsed":1075395},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664928251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13350,"timeElapsed":1089457},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664929945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1694,"timeElapsed":1091151},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664931290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1345,"timeElapsed":1092496},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664932683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1392,"timeElapsed":1093889},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664934504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1820,"timeElapsed":1095710},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664936079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1575,"timeElapsed":1097285},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664937583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1503,"timeElapsed":1098789},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664939127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1544,"timeElapsed":1100333},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664941312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2184,"timeElapsed":1102518},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664949897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7731,"timeElapsed":1111103},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664951052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1154,"timeElapsed":1112258},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664953650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2597,"timeElapsed":1114856},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664954972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1321,"timeElapsed":1116178},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664956553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1580,"timeElapsed":1117759},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664958088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1535,"timeElapsed":1119294},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664959810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1722,"timeElapsed":1121016},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664963912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4101,"timeElapsed":1125118},{"subjectID":"2ufa3g0wdf","prolificID":"5724e865386f1b0013e9563a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420d8cee988907232eceb","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665015655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":51743,"timeElapsed":1176861}]